

Vladyslav Nahornyi

Front-end Engineer

Vinnytsia, Ukraine +380968923137 · vnahornyi@outlook.com

Skype: logan0mcv,
Telegram: vnahornyidev,
Github: github.com/dosyao,
https://dosyao.github.io

Skills			
HTML			
css	_	_	_
SASS/LESS	_	_	_
React			
Redux			
MobX	_	_	
JavaScript			
TypeScript			
Next.js	_	_	
Node.js		_	
Git		_	
Agile/Scrun	n		_
Languages Ukrainian (I	Vative	·)	
Russian (Fl	uent)		
English (pre	e-inter	rmedi	ate)

Profile

Software engineer with 4 years of experience in 2 projects.

Strong professional skills in Front-end developing. Have experience with bootstrapping front-end from zero on React, Redux.

Bootstrapping layouts with Tailwind CSS or ChakraUI and customizing them. Adaptive site design. Work as HTML5 developer with mobile platforms. Have experience with JSON and worked with REST API.

My constant goal is to understand the client's business requirements and produce a maintainable code of high quality.

Employment History

Front-end Developer, EGO, Remote

August 2020 - October 2022

- · Layout creating.
- · Development of required features.
- Creating, updating UI components.
- · Perfomance optimization on front-end size.
- · Providing code review.

Tools: React, Next.js, Redux, MobX, TypeScript, Styled-Components, Next-Translate

Front-end Developer, WebTeam, Remote

August 2018 - July 2020

- · Development of required features.
- · Creating, updating UI components.
- · Application migration from jQuery to React.
- · Performance optimization on front-end side.

Tools: React, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, Less

Education

Bachelor, Vinnytsia National Technical University, Vinnytsia

September 2020 - Present

Telecommunications and radio engineering.

Software of telecommunication systems.